NAOMI MEININGER

nmeining18@gmail.com | 201.957.3868 | www.linkedin.com/in/naomi-meininger | https://github.com/naomi-meininger | https://naomi-meininger.github.io/personal_website/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer at Disney Streaming with internship experience at Major League Baseball and Blue Cross Blue Shield.Proven leader through project work with Tufts TAMID, service as Co-Chair of Disney Streaming's CDI Speaker Committee, and experience teaching computer science, leveraging a diverse skill set in management, programming, data analysis, and network security.

EXPERIENCE

Disney Streaming, Software Engineer I

Nov 2024 - Present

- Implement business infrastructure to migrate Hulu users to Disney's Advanced Commerce Platform (ACP) utilizing **Scala**, **Java**, **PostgreSQL**, **mySQLWorkBench**, and **DynamoDB**
- Build a Docker image and deploy it as a Kubernetes job in Spinnaker to create a cohort of migration users
- Identity billing discrepancies post migration using a Python script and alert other teams to issues found
- Fix bugs related to missing emails about subscription changes, subscription restart logic, and zero dollar invoices

Major League Baseball, Test Engineering Intern

lune 2024 - Aug 2024

- Implement **Playwright** tests for the MLB homepage and Home Run Derby Bracket using **JavaScript**, **GraphQL**, **Forge CMS**, **Apollo**, and **React**
- Develop integration tools for **TestRail** and **Slack** to upload **Playwright** test results directly to the platforms, utilizing **GitHub Actions**, **the TestRail API**, **the Slack API**, and **JUnit**
- Streamline automated testing for the All Star Ballot by adding data-testids to the React codebase

Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts, Full Stack Software Engineering Intern

June 2023 - Aug 2023

- Utilize Spring Boot, Selenium, Java, and Python to scrape LogRocket data and store it in PostgreSQL
- Develop a Random Forest Model to predict top 3 links for 5 insurance plans
- Create an Angular Service with Python backend to display links on BCBSMA homepage
- Enhance security and integrate endpoints using Spring Boot, Python, and Angular in MyBlue developer tools

Tufts University, Teaching Assistant for Computer Science

Aug 2021 - May 2024

- Conduct student instruction on recursion, pointers, and functional programming
- Manage office hours, grade assignments, lead a 26-person lab, and contribute to course infrastructure

Girls Who Code, Teaching Assistant for Summer Immersion Program

May 2022 - Aug 2022

- Teach HTML, CSS, and JavaScript while fostering sisterhood and promoting female representation in STEM

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Scala, C++, C, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Typescript, PHP, LaTex, SQL

Tools + Frameworks: IO, Node, Angular, React, Spring Boot, Flask, GraphQL, Apollo, npm, Yarn, Git, Jira, Confluence, SDKMAN, SBT

DevOps: Docker, Kubernetes, Spinnaker, Artifactory, Mariner, AWS, HPC, Heroku, Google Colab, Siteground, Intellij, VSCode

Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, DynamoDB, mySQLWorkBench, PgAdmin

Automation: Selenium, Beautiful Soup, Playwright, JUnit, TestRail, Gradle, Gitlab, Github Actions

Security: Wireshark, Nmap, Netcat, Scapy, Shodan, John the Ripper, Hashcat, Sqlmap, Burp Suite, apktool, Vault Secrets Management

Data Science + Machine Learning: Scikit-learn, Pandas, Tensorflow **Non-Native Languages:** Professional Working Spanish, Beginner Italian

PROJECTS

Hulu on Advanced Commerce Platform (Scala, Java, PostgreSQL, mySQLWorkBench, and DynamoDB)

- Implement APIs to migrate Legacy Hulu and Hulu through Sprint users to Disney's Advanced Commerce Platform (ACP) by cancelling their subscription on Hulu's legacy system and sending their credits (billing, support, gift) migration to ACP's unified credit service

Alarm (Python, Scapy)

- Develop a network incident detection tool that enables users to identify potential vulnerabilities and security breaches in network traffic using **live network streams** and **sets of PCAP files** for various security incidents

EDUCATION

Tufts University Sept 2020 – May 2024

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Minors in Mathematics and Theater, Magna Cum Laude

INTERESTS

Musical Theater, Disney, Sousaphone, Trivia, Community Outreach